bigcinemas.com 2011-02-08

# BIG Cinemas USA

BIG Cinemas has created this statement to explain its privacy and information gathering practices. We are sensitive to the private nature of information you provide to us over the Internet and are committed to responsible information handling practices. Our Privacy Policy is designed to maximize your ability to protect your personal information, while at the same time permit us to provide you the opportunity to obtain useful information, products and services. You are not obligated to provide us any personal information and if at any time you no longer wish to receive communications from us, you are free to "opt-out" of receiving these communications. Because this Privacy Policy applies to any person who provides information to BIG Cinemas through its website, we strongly urge you to fully review this Privacy Policy. Your use of this website constitutes acceptance of this Privacy Policy and any other applicable terms. 

Your use of the BIG Cinemas website or the Service signifies acknowledgement of and agreement to our Privacy Policy. You further acknowledge and agree that BIG Cinemas may, in its sole discretion, preserve or disclose your Content, as well as your information, such as email addresses, IP addresses, timestamps, and other user information, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: comply with legal process; enforce the TOU; respond to claims that any Content violates the rights of third-parties; respond to claims that contact information (e.g. phone number, street address) of a third-party has been posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; protect the rights, property, or personal safety of BIG Cinemas, its users or the general public. 

**Our Collection Of Your Information**

In order to enable you to register to receive information, products or services available through our website, or to permit us to respond to your inquiries, our site's registration forms may require that you provide contact information (such as your name, phone number and/or e-mail address), demographic information (such as your zip code or age) and/or financial information (such as account or credit card numbers). Our surveys may ask you for contact information, demographic information and lifestyle-related information (such as your interests, pastimes, buying preferences, etc). We may run contests on our site in which visitors are asked for contact and/or demographic information. We may also gather the Internet Protocol address and e-mail address of visitors to our website and the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail. In addition to this personal information, our web servers automatically collect website usage information from you when you visit our site. 

**Our Use Of Your Information**

Overall, we seek to use information collected through our website to enhance the experience of visitors to our site. BIG Cinemas, its affiliates or partners may use this information in a variety of ways, including:

To supply you with information, products or services you have requested, or to otherwise contact you about BIG Cinemas or its affiliates, their products, services, advertising, upcoming events, special offers or promotions, or for other purposes disclosed when you submit your information to our website.

  * To facilitate us in marketing and advertising our products and services and those of other businesses.
  * To improve the content and navigation on our website.
  * To prevent and detect fraud, infringement, and other potential misuse of our website.

To provide you with products or services you have requested, we may share your information, to possibly include personally identifiable information or information maintained on an aggregate basis, with third parties who provide services to BIG Cinemas and its affiliates, such as credit card processing, customer services, order fulfillment and/or prize delivery, as applicable.

We do not share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure - typically by opting in to receive information from a third party that is participating in a sweepstakes or other promotion on one of our websites. If you do not want your information to be used by a third party for direct marketing purposes (or other purposes unrelated to the uses described herein), do not opt in to such use by that third party. Please note that if you opt in to receive direct marketing from a third party, your information will be subject to that party’s privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact that third party directly. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.

**Promotions And Offers**

Product promotions are valid only for the time stated in the promotional materials. Promotions are subject to all the limitations stated in those published materials and agreed upon in the individual product or service contracts for the promoted products or services. BIG Cinemas is the sole judge of eligibility for any product promotion or offer on PhoenixTheatres.com and reserves the right to withdraw or amend any product or service promotion or offer at any time, without notification to any party.

**Children's Guidelines**

BIG Cinemas does not specifically target its online services to children under 18 years old. If you are under the age of 18 you may use our website only under the supervision of a parent or guardian. Please note that our site may contain links to content providers that collect information from children under the age of 18. We have no control over such content providers and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites. Because the Internet offers open access to a wide range of information, it is important that parents supervise and prevent access to inappropriate content, email or other such communication sessions.

**Cookies**

Our website uses cookies to track your favorite locations. Cookies are lines of text transmitted to your Web browser when you click on a site. They provide a way for a server to recall a prior request or previous registration so that information does not have to be reinserted. Your browser then stores the information on your hard drive and when you return to that site later, the cookie is transmitted back only to the servers that originally sent it to you. A cookie does not collect or keep your name or other personally identifying information; though we may link the information obtained through cookies to other personally identifiable information to give us a better understanding of your preferences, so we may provide a more meaningful experience to you on our site. To be notified when you are about to receive a cookie, your browser can be configured to alert you when a site is attempting to send you a cookie and at that time you will have the option of refusing it. Refer to your browser's "Help" function for more information and details. Advertisers that serve ads on our website may also utilize their own cookies. These cookies collect their own information independent of Big Cinemas activities. You can disable this cookie capability as described above.

**Third-party Sites**

Our website does contain links to other websites that we believe you might find useful and informative. Please note that BIG Cinemas does not endorse or recommend these sites' content or services, and that BIG Cinemas is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites. We encourage you review the privacy policies of each site you visit. The statements in this Privacy Policy apply solely to information collected by BIG Cinemas.

The BIG Cinemas site and Content available through the Service may contain features and functionalities that may link you or provide you with access to third party content which is completely independent of BIG Cinemas, including web sites, directories, servers, networks, systems, information and databases, applications, software, programs, products or services,and the Internet as a whole. 

Your interactions with organizations and/or individuals found on or through the Service, including payment and delivery of goods or services, and any other terms, conditions, warranties or representations associated with such dealings, are solely between you and such organizations and/or individuals.  You should make whatever investigation you feel necessary or appropriate before proceeding with any online or offline transaction with any of these third parties.

You agree that BIG Cinemas shall not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage of any sort incurred as the result of any such dealings. If there is a dispute between participants on this site, or between users and any third party, you understand and agree that BIG Cinemas is under no obligation to become involved. In the event that you have a dispute with one or more other users, you hereby release BIG Cinemas, its officers, employees, agents and successors in rights from claims, demands and damages (actual and consequential) of every kind or nature, known or unknown, suspected and unsuspected, disclosed and undisclosed, arising out of or in any way related to such disputes and / or our service. 

**Indemnification**

You agree to indemnify and hold BIG Cinemas, its officers, subsidiaries, affiliates, successors, assigns, directors, officers, agents, service providers, suppliers and employees, harmless from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorney fees and court costs, made by any third party due to or arising out of Content you submit, post or make available through the Service, your use of the Service, your violation of the TOU, your breach of any of the representations and warranties herein, or your violation of any rights of another.

**Security**  
  
We take every precaution to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. As a result, while we will strive to protect your personal communications and information, we cannot fully ensure or warrant that your private communications and personal information will not be disclosed to third parties. We will maintain appropriate safeguards, including technical measures, warnings, and firewalls, to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of any customer information under our control.

**Feedback And Contact Information**

We appreciate your comments and questions regarding this Privacy Policy.. If you would like to contact us regarding this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your interaction with this site, please write or call us at:

**BIG Cinemas**  
380 Madison Ave 21st Floor  
New York, NY 10017

**Policy Modifications**

We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted here, so please check back periodically for updates. Your continued use of our website after any change has been posted constitutes acceptance of the change to this Privacy Policy.

**Website**

BIG Cinemas reserves the right to make changes to our site and these disclaimers, terms, and conditions at any time.

**Our Corporate Address :**

**BIG Cinemas**  
380 Madison Ave 21st Floor  
New York, NY 100175

Copyright ©2008 BIG Cinemas. All rights reserved.   
This privacy policy was last updated April 22, 2009
